<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[wildmind.space]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>http://wildmind.space</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 03:31:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Catwoman, NOT catlady]]></title><description><![CDATA[I had to go to the supermarket tonight for some cat food. My cat, you see, is rather high maintenance and requires special food. While at…]]></description><link>http://wildmind.space/cat &amp; frozen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://wildmind.space/cat &amp; frozen/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 23:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I had to go to the supermarket tonight for some cat food. My cat, you see, is rather high maintenance and requires special food. While at the store, however, I realixed I should perhaps buy some food for next week. I do a little light cooking, most of the time, but I generally deplore cooking. Worse, if I devote time to cooking, I have less time to devote to my various writing projects, paintings, yoga, running, reading, and because I need it: chilling. So lately, to squeeze everythign in, I’ve been going to bed around 1 or 1:30 am. It’s not sustainable. By Thursday I feel like I’ve been hit by a truck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I caved tonight, mesmerized by the flourescent glow and the clear glass dividing me and Amy’s organic frozen lunches. Palak Paneer. Vegetable Korma. Poblano Enchilada. I wouldn’t have to cook as much, I would be able to sleep more and still run and stretch and let my imagine go wild at my little drafting table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when I arrived at the checkout counter, on this cool and breezy Friday eve, I looked down into my basked and saw:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cat litter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canned cat food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dry cat food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oatmeal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frozen lunches for a week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was, of course, delicately horrified. Was I turning into an old, solitary, catlady already? It sure looked like it. Any cashier would assume so, and I wouldn’t fault them for it. What has my life become? I’m only 35! (Which simultaneously feels too old and too young for all the circumstances of my existence as of late). I felt dizzy with a mild sort of panic, the flourescent light suddenly entering my eyeballs in such a fashion that they were forced more and more widely open. But I snapped back into it (into a placid reality, that is), and calmly placed my items on the counter. I keep telling myself: whatever shape my life takes, I must do my best to enjoy it. I don’t get another and there are no guarantees on this one either. Though I must admit I secretly said to myself: “This isn’t your life forever, Katie, this is your life right now, for this while.” And that made me feel better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing lasts forever. Not the good, not the shit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I’ll get around to re-designing and re-coding this website. But it’ll be a long, slow process. As outlined above, my days are already, let’s say, superfluous, despite it being just me and my overweight feline companion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a catwoman, thanks, not a cat lady. Not yet, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love,
KD&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[what is wild mind? why .space? hello! wild mind is katie duane’s personal development space for all
things creative. I chose the domain…]]></description><link>http://wildmind.space/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://wildmind.space/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;what is wild mind? why .space?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;hello! wild mind is katie duane’s personal development space for all
things creative. I chose the domain “wild mind” simply because that best
describes her mind type. it is all over the place, and not always in a
“bad” way: I am curious about and love everything from flowers and rocks
to learning about ancient ice sheets, asteroid composition, lunar history,
the meanings of colors, and …more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I usually attempt to express this wide-ranging curiosity through the
making of art: be it visual or written, and sometime via projects on the
web too! Obviously, this one is in its infancy, and rather hideous atm.
It’ll get there, and when it does, it will be my casita on the web for
writing and sharing: thoughts, drawings, works-in-progress, and
published/polished pieces, as they trickle in. I chose .space because I
love outer space, wide-open spaces, and is a little spacey, myself. my
father used to refer to me as “space cadet”, and ask whether I was on
pluto, or earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;come back soon! cheers!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>